<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My Projects on Joaquin Jerez</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My Projects on Joaquin Jerez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Aliquam</title>
      <link>/blogs/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:42:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/aliquam/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tempus</title>
      <link>/blogs/tempus/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/tempus/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Magna</title>
      <link>/blogs/magna/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/magna/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cornell Baja Racing</title>
      <link>/blogs/baja/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/baja/</guid>
      <description>Who we are In my freshmen year at Cornell, I applied for the Cornell Baja Racing team. In my first semester, I joined the brakes team. &amp;ldquo;Cornell Baja SAE Racing is an engineering project team which annually designs, builds and races an off-road vehicle to compete in the SAE Collegiate Baja Design Series. By encouraging hands-on engineering and project-based learning, Cornell Baja takes engineering out of the classroom (and onto the track) for 40 students annually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hoplite: Medical Drone Delivery Start-Up</title>
      <link>/blogs/hoplite/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/hoplite/</guid>
      <description>Our goal Two Cornell Engineers and I got together September 2019 and set out to build a venture that would save people&amp;rsquo;s lives. We conducted months of empathy fieldwork to find how we could best apply our skills to achieve that goal.
Problem Sudden Cardiac Arrest (SCA) is the leading cause of death in America, killing around 325,000 people every year. This leads to many deaths because you only have about 10 minutes to receive treatment via an automated external defibrillator (AED) before your survival rate drops to zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poloma Analytics</title>
      <link>/blogs/poloma/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 21:28:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/poloma/</guid>
      <description>Sample Content Praesent ac adipiscing ullamcorper semper ut amet ac risus. Lorem sapien ut odio odio nunc. Ac adipiscing nibh porttitor erat risus justo adipiscing adipiscing amet placerat accumsan. Vis. Faucibus odio magna tempus adipiscing a non. In mi primis arcu ut non accumsan vivamus ac blandit adipiscing adipiscing arcu metus praesent turpis eu ac lacinia nunc ac commodo gravida adipiscing eget accumsan ac nunc adipiscing adipiscing.
Sem turpis amet semper Nunc lacinia ante nunc ac lobortis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainable Mobility</title>
      <link>/blogs/cusd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/cusd/</guid>
      <description>Who we are The Sustainable Mobility team of Cornell University Sustainable Design, formally Bus Shelter Renovations, is focused on redesigning public transportation in Tompkins County. We comprise of students from all seven colleges of Cornell University and are partnering with the Tompkins Consolidated Area Transit, TCAT, to develop a more systematic approach for urban-to-rural public transportation. As part of this systematic change, we utilize systems design thinking to understand and best serve the needs of our stakeholders.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>